♪ In the not too distant
Future ♪
♪ Somewhere in time and space ♪
♪ Mike Nelson
And his robot pals ♪
♪ Are caught in a nasty place ♪
♪ They try to survive
The wrath of Pearl ♪
♪ Just an evil gal
Who wants to rule the world ♪
♪ From her castle below
She sets her sights above ♪
♪ Just to torture
All the captives ♪
♪ On the Satellite of Love ♪
- Get me down!
- ♪ I'll send him
Cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst I can find
La-la-la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
And watch them all ♪
♪ And I'll monitor his mind
La-la-la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Mike can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies begin or end
La-la-la ♪
♪ He'll try to
Keep his sanity ♪
♪ With the help of
his robot friends ♪
- ♪ Robot roll call ♪
♪ Cambot! ♪
- ♪ You're on! ♪
- ♪ Gypsy! ♪
- ♪ Oh, my stars! ♪
- ♪ Tom Servo! ♪
- ♪ Check me out! ♪
- ♪ Croooow! ♪
- ♪ I'm different! ♪
♪ If you're wondering
How he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts
La-la-la ♪
♪ Just repeat to yourself ♪
♪ It's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
- Oh yeah, that's nice.
You are a miracle worker,
my friend.
- Hi everyone,
Mike Nelson here.
Welcome to
the Satellite of Love,
I'm here with Tom Servo
and Crow T. Robot.
Hey, what you got there, Crow?
- Oh, that's my
W.W.B.S.M.D bracelet.
Whenever I find myself
at a moral crossroads--
which happens a lot, okay?
I remember my bracelet,
look down, I ask myself,
"What would
Buffy Sainte-Marie Do?"
Then I'm able to get
my moral bearings.
- Okay, okay.
Say you had a friend,
or say Mike here.
And he comes to you wearing
a hideous outfit, so yeah, Mike,
and he's just about to
go on a date.
- So, it wouldn't be Mike,
would it?
- But anyway, he asks you to
tell him honestly how he looks.
Do you lie and let him
make a fool out of himself?
Or do you tell him the truth
and risk hurting his feelings?
- Huh.
I would write a folk song!
Any other dilemmas
I can help you guys with?
- No, we're okay.
We'll be right back.
♪ Hey little bird
I remember you... ♪
[LAUGHING]
- Go on and play
your silly games.
You won't be laughing
after I become a fully
accredited mad scientist.
[SINISTER LAUGH]
Right after this.
[♪♪♪]
- So anyway, that's what
Jerry Jeff Walker would do.
- He sounds like
a man of great character.
Crow, what's the bracelet
with all the "W"s stand for?
- Oh, this stands for
the "What would the World
Wide Wrestling Federation,
Woodrow Wilson,
Wet Willy, Wesley Willis,
Wade Wilson,
William Wyler,
Wendy Wasserstein,
Walt Whitman,
Willy Wonka,
Wim Wenders..."
- Okay, alright, okay, can it.
Pearl's calling us.
- "...do."
[MUMBLING]
- Oh, boy!
That is most unpleasant.
And... [indistinct]
- So Nelson,
once I'm finished with you,
I'll return to the Institute
with proof, proof,
that it was they who are mad.
Mad for not seeing the potential
behind my grandest experiment.
[LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
- Pearl?
What the Samuel Langhorne hell
are you talking about?
- What am I talking about?
Why, nothing less than
world domination.
- Okay, Pearl.
I think I've got
a pretty good idea
of what you're capable of,
I'm just gonna make some notes.
- Okay. Great,
take any space you need.
- Thank you.
- Hey morons,
sorry about all that.
I gotta get board certified
with the Institute
of Mad Scientists.
I didn't know it, but it's
illegal to rule the world
if you're not board certified.
Brain Guy?
- Yes, Madame?
- I wanted to give you a hump.
- Look, whatever your feelings
are for me, I think...
- On your back, idiot.
- That's sexual harassment
and I don't have to take it.
- A latex hump.
- Now see here! That's...
- Would you just put this on?
- Okay, well,
why don't you show me
how you plan to
take over the world,
and I'll throw in
if I have any questions.
- Okay, super.
I'll just call my subject.
Nelson?
Prepare to be tortured
by my maddest creation yet.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Your movie is wrenched from--
wrenched from hell itself.
It's called,
Girl in Gold Boots?
- Okay then, Pearl.
- I am trying to get
accredited.
Could you please
help me out here.
Yes, the mephitic
Girl in Gold Boots.
- Madness!
[SCREAMING]
- It's madness!
It's madness!
[SINISTER LAUGHING]
- Master...
- Ow, ow!
Oh, mercy, mercy.
Say? Isn't anybody
gonna shock me back here?
What's going on?
I don't...
- No!
[CRYING]
- Would you cut it out?
[BUZZER]
- Alright.
Oh, movie sign!
[BLUES MUSIC]
- Oh yeah, geez.
- Oh, I'm sorry,
I'm projecting my dreams again.
- Heh heh.
- They're gonna sock it to us.
[♪♪♪]
- She may damage her bippy
if she keeps doing that.
- Panty-vision.
- Ow.
Shouldn't we be in individual
booths for this movie?
- Annie forgot her gold boots.
She's in trouble.
- It's a jerk and pony marathon.
- The dancers are wearing
oven bags.
- An injured reserve,
Mary Wells.
- Hey.
[LAUGHS]
- Hey, those are street shoes
on the gym floor.
- Mike, you're a human being,
how come you don't
have a body like that?
- Yeah.
- Wow, wow, wow.
- The Kennedy Center tribute
to Judy Carne.
- To the G,
to the G chord, men, now!
Yeah.
- Ed Grimley
choreographed this dance.
- H.R. Pufnstuf's
go go girl review.
- Whoo.
[♪♪♪]
- Not my sacrilily, ow, ow.
- Why does Noam Chomsky insist
these women open for him?
- Ma'am, could we get a menu
or just some pretzels, please?
- Boy, the first
Lilith Fair was weird.
- Mosh pit!
- Everybody do the agitated
cycle, mm mm mm.
- ♪ Everything I touch
Turns to gold ♪
- What happens
when you touch gold?
- ♪ Everything I touch
Turns to gold ♪
- Everything I touch
turns to flies.
- Wolfgang Puck's sad demise.
- Yeah, I've gotta test out
my frying medium
before I use it.
- I forgot the me.
- Ah, the nights we'd linger
over brandy at "Eat."
- Luci Baines Johnson
shaking her tail feathers.
- It's a neighbor
from the next county
asking him
to turn down the music.
- Oh! What manner of loaf
will I have tonight?
- What the-- oh, a gun.
So that was the loud report
and burning sensation
in my groin.
- Can I talk to someone
about catering a bar mitzvah?
[♪♪♪]
- Did you have
the puffer fish tonight?
[♪♪♪]
- I'm Casey Kasem.
- Thanks for the dance,
jukebox.
- Don't, the fryer's
hooked up to the clapper.
- How long have you
been there?
- As long as I've been
anywhere else.
- Long enough to see
that you've got a good act.
- Well, I bet you came in here
for something besides the show.
- Yes, I need a puffy hat
with a filthy saying.
- I should tell you
it's my birthday.
- As a matter of fact I can...
- Sorry we shot you
back there, Mr. Hopper.
- So I was saying,
I came in here
for a piece of apple pie
and a cup of coffee.
- Can I sit inside
and have a car seat next time?
- El Kabong is stalking them.
[indistinct]
- You forgot to take
the microphone out of the box.
- Why do you ask?
- Afternoon, fair lady,
kind, sir.
Any idea where California went?
- I'll check my purse.
- It went thatta way, partner.
- Straight down this here road
a piece?
[indistinct]
...just beyond Arizona?
- Alright.
- I have five mighty hungry
companions with me on this trip.
Appetites you can't imagine.
ALL COMMENTATORS:
Ew.
- Oh, I'll sell you
anything in the place, Mister.
- Take me, take me.
- I'll settle for
10 Hershey bars, please.
- 10 Hershey bars?
Those are hard to eat.
- Heh-heh.
We bantered.
- That'll be one dollar.
- I'm got a happenings coupon.
- Can you cash 100?
- I've never even seen one.
- Oh, I'll have 1,000
Hershey bars then, I guess.
- Oh lucky me,
here's a single.
- Did he just say, "licky me?"
- Goodbye, fair Guinevere.
I must hasten on to
the land of milk and honey.
- Hey, wait a minute.
- Somebody call
for a cab to LaGuardia?
- He here for you, friend?
- Hey, I'm not a Quaker.
- That's Jimmy.
He's always... [indistinct]
- Ew, that brought
the room down.
- Goodbye, fair cowboy knight,
I guess.
[♪♪♪]
- You're really hooked
on this dancing, aren't you?
- Look, I have ergotism.
- Hey, ever thought of
being a professional?
- I guess I'd give about
anything in the world to be one.
- I can help you.
- You can help me.
- Sure.
Look, my sister's an underwater
attraction in Los Angeles
in a groovy
Hollywood nightclub.
Let me show you.
There she is,
my sister Joan Nichols.
- This is your sister?
- Yup.
- She's really nude.
- Go on.
You're a bigger nut
than he was.
- Well, hold on now.
- And if you buy now,
you also get the Cap Snaffler.
- Same girl.
- After Rustoleum.
- Listen, I'm on my way
to Hollywood right now.
Now why don't you come with me
and I'll bet you
my sister can make you
into a star, just like that.
And I'll do all of that
for you
in exchange for
a little companionship.
You know what I mean,
like being my relief driver.
I want to drive
straight through.
- Want to drive
- Oh, boy. Have you got
a line a mile long.
- Hey, I'm serious.
- I'm sure you are.
Look, I may have stars
in my eyes,
I don't believe
everything I hear.
- Help? Come in here.
- And bring the baby wipes.
- Excuse me.
[♪♪♪]
- Girl, I told you
an hour ago
to get them
pots and pans washed.
- Daddy, I've got
a customer out front.
- Mmm.
- Get me a bucket.
- You do them dirty dishes
and I'll take care of the front.
- No, please.
- What did you say?
- Mr. Johnson hired me
to take care of the front
and you to take care
of the kitchen.
You want to get us fired again?
- Don't you get smart with me!
- I'm not getting smart.
- I can't.
- It's just that
you've been drinking.
You're going out there
and making a fool of yourself
anyway.
- 'Cause I excrete oil?
- Okay, I've been drinking.
I slopped up
a few stinking beers,
I ain't good enough to be
your father no more, huh?
- Daddy, please!
- Whatta ya mean,
"Daddy, please?"
[COMMENTATORS LAUGHING]
- You afraid I'm gonna breath
on some of your lousy
studs out there?
Is that it?
- That's enough!
- You no good tramp,
you're just like your mother.
- You're right.
I am like her and I'm glad.
At least she had enough guts
to get away from you.
[CRIES OUT]
- Hey, they have tacos.
- My father passed away.
I stuck his head
in the deep fryer.
- What's wrong?
- I just found out
what's in the special sauce.
- You know
what this place needs?
A business card jar.
- You still want someone
to go to Hollywood with?
- 'Cause my dad wants to go.
- You bet I do.
- Help yourself
to another cup of coffee
while I get some things packed.
- Pepsi paid handsomely
for this product placement.
- Okay, I can have coffee.
Am I implicitly allowed
to take cream as well?
- Maybe I should have
a poetry slam on Wednesdays.
- Sure hope sis still swings
at that spot on Sunset.
- I've packed
like 50 cheeseburgers.
- Um, Michele, look, I guess
I better come clean with you.
There is another reason
I asked you along.
- I know.
We can fight about that later.
- No, no, no.
Look, I'll treat you any way
you want to be treated.
Fair enough?
- You were serious, weren't you?
- Sure, sure I was serious.
But-- Well, there is
one minor complication.
- I smell like ham.
- I ain't got enough bread
for gas all the way to L.A.
Will you be able to help
in that department too?
- I'm gonna go get
a goodbye slap from dad.
- So, no one called a taxi?
- I took a toothpick,
we can sell it
for traveling money.
- Bye, dad.
- Michelle?
- Oh, guy's got
a severe under bite.
[SIREN]
- It's illegal
to not stop at Eat.
- Baby, I think
you're gonna be good for me.
The old luck
is changing already.
- Who am I?
Mrs. Khrushchev, he he he.
- And so passed
the "Eat" phase of my life.
[♪♪♪]
- No playing Jimmy Rogers.
- It's a car, heh.
- I gotta go, I gotta go.
- Can you stop for a second?
I have to dance.
- Comanches are watching.
- Ah, here we are at
"Drink, Boink, and Regret."
- So, whatta ya think
of Hollywood so far?
- Snack time.
Anything special you want?
- Yeah, a place
to comb my hair.
- Eh, there's probably an
intensely foul bathroom there.
- I'll see what they have.
- Start seeing motorcycles, see?
- Come on, move it!
- Hey man,
you ready for move it?
- You are a delight.
- My baseball card
fell out of my spokes.
- You meet the nicest people
on a Honda.
- Welcome to nothing
but Jerky.
- Uh, we've talked it over.
I was ready for "move it,"
but my friend here
had some reservations.
- Would you like to
take his brains out
and play with 'em, now?
- We'll have none of those
shenanigans in here.
You come in for what
you wanted and leave.
- There's no problem, ma'am.
No problem.
- Look, she's thinking of Coke.
- That's just his breath.
- Wow, they have Bomb Pops!
- In my panic, I bought
nothing but napkins.
- Where will I comb?
- Tonight is kinda special.
- You know, it's okay.
Couldn't possibly
make it more sticky.
- The bikers are still inside
flipping through Tikkun.
- When he sits there,
he's going to get Krausened.
- My God, Buz.
You're out of your mind.
Don't you know
they'll kill you for that?
- Don't you worry
your pretty head about it.
- Okay, ugly head.
- Let's get out of here quick.
- Drive in reverse and get
some of that gas back.
- Free beer!
Lick the bike.
- That punk with the chick.
- Want to snub him, man?
- You better believe it.
- We'll snub him.
Let's organize a party quick
and not invite him.
[CHUCKLES]
- Hey, wait for me.
My kickstand's stuck.
Wait, ow.
- They're gonna force him
to pay half
on a bottle of Armor All.
- Should of left some Chuckles
on his seat too.
- Hey, my butt is drunk.
- It's really upsetting
what he did to our bikes.
I feel anger and I don't know
how to direct it.
- First time I've driven with
my blood alcohol under two.
It's real easy.
- Roy, come back here
and pick that up.
- Shh! There's a bat
on the hood.
- Okay, you're a dancer.
Get out, bye.
- Keep the motor running.
- Check the oil,
wipe the windshield.
♪ Batman ♪
- He's giving himself
a drunk test.
- Starring Regis Philbin.
- Stay back,
he has a can of Grape Nehi.
- He's gonna hit him
with a garter snake.
[TOM BURPS]
- Clinton.
- I ain't gonna play
"Sun City."
- Let's go back to law school.
We're terrible bikers.
- Have fun.
- We're not gonna have fun now.
- I'm glad you're back.
I was locked in.
- I feel exhilarated.
Let's get a pony keg
and head to Sturgis.
- Hell's Pusses.
- What are we gonna do now, man?
- Why don't you just
shut your mouth?
- Why don't I have any friends?
- Hey guys.
- Yeah, Mike!
You're probably wondering
why I'm pissed off at you.
- Uh, no. Not really.
- Well, too bad.
I'm going to exact petty,
childish revenge on you.
Yeah, and I'm gonna
have to pour beer
on your most beloved object.
[LAUGHS]
- Eh, what is your most beloved
object, if you don't mind?
- Oh. Well, I'd have to say
my personalized
heirloom beer stein.
[SINISTER LAUGHING]
- Oh say, could you help me
exact revenge, please?
- Oh no, please, Crow, no...
sure.
- Okay okay, there.
Nice and easy like...
Yeah, take the beer there,
that's right,
and pour it
all over your stein!
- Oh no...
[PRETEND CRYING]
[SINSISTER LAUGHING]
- That's right, you're gonna get
what you got coming, Mr. Cool.
Teach you a lesson
in a big way.
- But Crow,
you're out of your mind.
Don't you know
he'll kill you for that?
- Ah, don't worry your pretty
little head about it, Servo.
- Hey Crow, you know
I should tell you that uh,
you are most beloved to me too.
You know that?
- Okay then, buddy.
You are going to take that beer
and throw it on me!
- But Crow...
- Do it!
- Yeah, that's right, loser.
You know you got it coming.
There you go.
[LAUGHS]
Revenge is sweet!
Okay, now get out of here,
you punk
and take your damn beer
with you.
- Okay, alright.
Well, I think
I learned my lesson.
See you, Crow.
[SINISTER LAUGHING]
- Now, that didn't pan out
quite the way I expected.
- Oh.
[♪♪♪]
- I'm sorry.
- I didn't mean to turn you on.
- Well, I said I was sorry.
- Look, I'm really remorseful,
you cow.
- Well, say something.
- I guess I was just tired.
- That's why I didn't really
do anything to make you mad.
- Come here.
- I need you to help me
to shift the Turbo-Hydramatic.
- Okay, you can sex me now.
- Ooo, he slips
off the babushka.
- And next comes the wig.
- Please accept my tongue
as an apology.
- Wait a minute,
one of your spacers
fell out again.
- Oh, wait.
It was a dream.
He's kissing his Budweiser.
- Nope.
Forget that scene, never mind.
- He should be
showing more leg.
- Yeah, someone else's leg.
- Yeah.
- Uh-oh.
- Hey, recognize him?
- Of course I do.
He's the guy
with all the words.
- You mean, he's the guy
with all the bread.
- Come on,
let's go pick him up.
- Words, bread, must be
Samuel Johnson with a baguette.
- The good Samaritans,
I presume.
- Need help?
- Yeah, I guess
you could say so.
Traveler here, my bike,
seems to have thrown a rod.
- Well now, seems to me
you got an awful lot of trouble
with that wreck.
Yesterday you had it
on the truck bed.
- Oh, yeah.
We've met before, haven't we?
Why, you my fair lady,
you're Guinevere.
But I don't seem to
recall your name, sir.
- Aw, cut the baloney out, huh?
You want a ride?
- My other name is Michele,
he's Buz.
- Michele and Buz.
- I'll allow it.
- Mine's Critter.
- Critter?
- Yeah, you know,
like a cowboy's horse
or a wayward cat
without a home.
- Look, come on.
You want a ride?
- Yes, we do.
- Whatta ya mean, we?
- Well, Traveler and I.
- Aw, now look, wise guy,
I ain't carrying no
beat up old motorcycle
on the back of my car.
- Well, you won't have to,
I got a tow bar.
- Oh, well, you got to have
an upper hitch
for one of them to work.
- Ah, it just so happens
I have one of those too.
- You know, in fact,
I have a car too,
so I guess
I don't need a ride.
- Three hours
and four bumpers later.
- We'll take the sidewalk
for another couple of miles.
- Now, they picked up Joan Baez.
- Is there a papoose
tied to the motorcycle.
- You know, I can't
get over your name.
It's a funny name, Critter.
- Fellas gave me that name
when I was in preschool.
- I'm back!
[ALL COMMENTATORS LAUGHING]
- I helped the native...
[indistinct]
- Yeah? You're kidding.
- Anybody notice
that I'm here now?
- ...I'll bet you got
a college education.
- Well, yes and no.
I didn't get a degree
but I tried my hand at
Columbia and Berkeley.
- Wish I could've gone
to one of them.
- Come on,
I just teleported here.
It's impressive!
- Look, I hate to butt in on
this real brilliant conversation
but we gotta
bing it outta here.
Waitress?
Check please.
Now how about it,
Critter, old pal?
It seems to me this place
oughta have change
for a 50,
maybe even a 100, huh?
- Three waters, those little
fish shaped soup crackers...
- I'm an icky elf.
- Ever since I got back,
I've been carrying my billfold
full of Nepalese money.
- From the land of nipple.
- But you can try to get it
cashed if you like.
- You tell funny
foreign currency jokes.
- I'm Critter. Eh?
- Okay baby,
show all yours.
- Here?
- Your money's from Senegal.
- 10 bucks?
That's all you've got?
- I had to buy...
[indistinct]
- But you were back
at a cash register.
- And took what was
coming to me.
It amounted to 14 dollars.
- Well, that's just great.
- You didn't have to
take out FICA.
- With this tab coming to 4.50,
that'll leave us a lousy 5.50
to get to L.A.
- Look, I didn't take any more
from the cash register
than 14 dollars.
That was mine.
- That was my yearly salary.
- Okay boy, can you take care
of your own share?
- Yeah.
- Natural born cheapskates.
- I can come up
with my own share.
- Uh, here's some
Guatemalan quetzal.
- And 15 dollars more to boot.
- Why, we oughta be able to
reach Los Angeles with 20 bucks.
- Come on.
- Let's get some of those
pillowy little mints
at the cash register.
- Well, I should get a little
to go box and my butter pat.
- He yanked the engine
off a KitchenAid blender.
[CROW SCREAMS]
He's throwing us violently
into the next scene.
- Hi, can I be in your movie?
- This makes me want to throw
hard candy at people.
- So, they blew the 15 bucks
on a dune buggy rental.
- We're thinking of adopting.
- A new motorized
beach bathtub.
- And the movie ends.
No.
- Let's drive through
the oil soaked ducks again.
[SCREAMING]
- Well, apparently the story
is none of our business.
- What a ride!
- Enjoyed it?
Hey, you wanna go for a ride?
- Uh, no.
I guess I'll pass for now.
Thanks a lot.
- Alright.
- Well, I don't know
about you guys, but...
- I'm an icky elf.
- ...I'm thirsty.
- So long, odd acquaintance,
who inexplicably gave us
rides in your dune buggy.
- There goes...
- You can say that a...
- One o...
- You and Buz planned
to get married in L.A.?
- You don't need to
spell in front of me.
- I'm riding with him to L.A.
He's going to help me
get started as a dancer.
His sister can help me.
That's all there is to it.
- Well, my naive country girl,
I hope it's that simple.
- Uh-huh.
I'm gonna be a dancer.
- Maybe Buz does seem
a little crude at times,
but you just have to
get to know him.
- It helps if you meet
the other elf.
- Like two days?
Hey...
- My name's Critter.
- ...don't pay any attention
to me.
What you do
is your own business
and it's really
no concern of mine.
- That's right,
it is no concern of yours.
I'm going to become a dancer,
Critter, and a good one.
You said yourself I'm pretty.
I'm good at dancing too.
- Compared to Stephen Hawking.
- ...when you're wet
and angry... [indistinct]
- Critter, stop teasing me.
I want you to take me seriously.
- Okay, little numby head.
- I'm taking you seriously.
- Thank you. Anyway,
the thing about dancing
is when you dance...
[MUFFLED SOUNDS]
- Hey, he's mine,
take your hands off him!
- Get lost.
[SHOUTS]
- Stop it, please!
- I'm having Critter's varmint.
- Listen you, you stay away
from Michele, understand?
- Why don't you
let her decide that?
- Yeah.
Why not?
- Are you only here
in California to... [indistinct]
broken down old motorcycle
or are you here
for a reason?
Now you tell him.
[SHOUTS]
- I'm allergic to shellfish.
- I'm here to be a dancer!
- Going to go
into voice work too.
- Well, now the whole picnic
is ruined.
- I'm a crumby Critter.
[♪♪♪]
- We're in Alberta,
it looks like.
- Find your number?
- Uh, yeah.
- Will this be cash or charge?
- Uh, will you take
a toothpick?
- Cash.
- On second thought,
I'll just put it on my gun.
- Hey, that guy's totally
pistol whipped, man.
- Oh, he flicked a booger.
- Oh shoot,
it's all green stamps.
- Sounds like Max and 99
should be sneaking
around outside.
- Don't forget your
Roman Gabriel collector's plate.
- Oh shoot,
they're closed-- oh.
- I locked the car keys
in the store.
- Did you get
my Marathon Bar?
- Hey, what the devil's
going on?
- Stay in the car.
Get behind the wheel.
- Get more behind the wheel,
come on.
- Where's the attendant?
- Sound asleep.
Okay, roll this baby
out of here.
- Buz, what have you done?
Have you gone crazy?
- Move it!
- I've got 50 bucks.
We've got dune buggy rides
all week.
- Hey, crimes like this
never happen anymore
now that we have McGruff.
- I hope we're here
in time for folk rock.
- Hey, they drove straight
to Christmas Village
to blow the wad.
[CHRISTMAS MUSIC]
♪ Oh it's lovely weather
For a surfboard ♪
♪ Together with you ♪
♪ Where the Bank of America
Whoa ho ♪
[♪♪♪]
- A bunny from heaven.
- Hey pally, huh!
- Dr. Doolittle?
That doesn't look like
Eddie Murphy.
- No.
- I think someone slipped us
their vacation videos.
- Okay, keep it coming.
I'm not convinced
that they're in L.A. yet.
- An 18-story office building?
This could only be L.A.
♪ Oh Charles Manson
Walks the streets ♪
♪ The Zodiac killer's at large ♪
♪ Charles Bukowski
Is puking out the window ♪
♪ And Santa Claus
Is on his way ♪
- Hey!
- Merry Christmas everyone,
let's go to the haunted house.
- Boo, sir.
- Thanks for the car, buddy.
- Yup, I know
the werewolf here.
[BLUES MUSIC]
- Wow, this is like
"Eat," times four.
- Love this.
- Yeah, see how they
shake their boobs.
- Man, think of the lucky kid
who stumbles on
this haunted house.
- Yeah-hah.
Look, something.
- Stacy Keach.
- Table for three.
- Uh, butts or breasts?
- Would you like to sit down?
- Get lost.
- I've worked here
six year, sir.
It's gonna be hard to find
a place I don't know about.
- Is that my friend,
Count Chocula?
- You enjoying the show, pal?
- Yeah.
- You guys are broke,
go home and watch
the late night movie on TV.
- Do you know if
Van Ryan's Express is on?
- Now don't get cute, son.
- Or my doppelganger
will kick you out.
- The Mt. Rushmore of ugly.
- We're just waiting for
the show to get over with.
That's my sister up there.
The one in the middle?
- The one who just
fell off the stage?
- D-- Donna?
Where are you going?
- Bye Cindy, good luck!
[APPLAUSE]
- Thank you,
I'm the one who jumped.
Thank you.
- This show made possible
by a grant from
the Onan Foundation.
- Hey, I forgot to tell you
about our pasta special.
- Follow me.
- What?
Ah ah ah... choo.
Ah ah ah...
[♪♪♪]
♪ You and I... ♪
- Now they're singing
"Keep Your Brown Chukka
Boots Moving Yeah Guy."
- I don't dance,
I just kinda walk in place.
- I'll direct you to
the dancer's brother's lounge.
- Oh man.
The duct tape did not
come off easy tonight.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
- Hey, Joanie.
You got visitors.
- Who is it, Liam?
- Oh, come on, sis.
Open up the door.
[SHOUTING INCOHERENTLY]
[CROW IMITATES SHOUTING]
- Why didn't you tell me
you were coming?
Oh, friends of yours?
- Yeah, they're moving
to California with me.
This is Michele Casey,
Critter Jones.
- Glad to meet you,
Miss Nichols.
- Hello, Michele.
Oh, pretty.
Hello, Critter.
- Hi, Miss Nichols.
- Come in, come in.
Sit down. Sit down.
- Sit down!
- Oh, you met Leo, I guess.
- Well, no.
Not officially.
- Mr. Sayer?
- Oh.
Well, I want you all to meet
my one and only, Leo McCabe.
Leo owns the place.
- I blink at you.
- Well, now that we got
the greetings settled, brother,
tell me, what are you doing
out here on the coast?
Did you finally get
in some serious trouble?
- Are you kidding?
None of those good citizens
are hip enough to catch me.
- The fuzz may be numb
where you come from, friend,
but they're pretty well with it
on the Hollywood scene.
- Nice pants.
- Give me.
- Give you what?
- You lay that gun on me,
sweetheart.
- Buz, my God!
Are you carrying...
- Cool it!
- I'm talking to sweetheart.
- I'm not going count, sonny.
Now.
- That makes me shiny.
- I enjoy your pants as well.
- Somewhere Charlton Heston
is weeping.
- When do I get it back?
- You don't.
There're only a few people
in this town
who pack these things,
and most of 'em are cops.
If you need some bread,
I can help you.
But I don't like bad men
and kids with guns.
Dig?
- I guess that's groovy.
- You come in my office
and we'll talk, okay?
[indistinct]
- That's my favorite breed
of Chinese dog.
- Thank God he didn't notice
my weird pushed in face.
- Don't let him bug you, Buz.
- Oh, I'm not bugged,
I just forgot
I was in someone else's
ballpark for a moment.
- Started playing bongo.
- What about you, Michele?
You gonna be moving on
with Critter?
- Nah, she's with me.
- Oh.
- Joanie,
I want to be a dancer.
- Sis, you ought to
see her dance.
She is just great.
I told her you're gonna
help her get started.
- Thanks.
- Does she have any
investment metal boots?
- Just try me.
I'll work, really I will.
- Well, um...
- There is a breast shortage
in L.A.
- ...we'll take a look at you
tomorrow.
- Just an audition,
that's all I ask.
- Oh okay,
we'll audition you tomorrow.
- You need a bra fitter at all?
- Looks as if you folks pretty
well have your future set.
I feel like the Lone Ranger,
riding off looking after folks
that are gonna live
happily ever after.
- Well met, fair Critter.
- So long.
Thanks for the buggy ride.
- Anytime, yak boy.
- Thanks, Alpaca man.
- Road kill, wait!
- You sure she's with you?
- Yeah, in a way
that makes her look
like she's with other guys.
[♪♪♪]
[BLUES MUSIC]
- Yeah, alright, baby.
Shake what your momma
gave you, yeah!
- Hey Tom, have you seen
the scotch tape--
What the well
is going on in here?
- Well, we set up a little
club here, Mike.
Good times, man.
- But Crow is-- is...
- Shaking his money maker,
that's right.
Go baby!
- Oh, I'm going.
Check this out, watch.
- Oh yeah!
Shake your good stuff, baby.
- But Crow, he's shaking
all his various things
and he has a tiny
gold bikini on.
- Not for long.
- Yeah, but first you have to
stuff money in it.
- Oh yeah.
Mike, get my bag.
We gotta start stuffing.
I got a roll of singles in there
as big as a pork roast.
- No, no. Crow will keep
all his clothes on
no matter
how miniscule they are.
- I don't even usually
wear clothes, Mike.
What's your deal?
- I think you're uncomfortable
acknowledging Crow
as a sexual being.
- He's not a sexual being,
he's a robot and so are you.
- You have such
body issues, Mike.
- Mike Taliban Nelson.
- You know, I'm sorry if you're
ashamed of your body, Mike,
we are not.
- Ashamed of our bodies,
that is.
We are ashamed of yours.
- That's right.
Here I go!
Watch this.
- Yeah, have a little of that.
- No, stop it, stop it!
In the name of all
that is good and decent...
- Here's the good stuff.
- Oh, oh God!
- Oh yeah!
Hey, bartender, hook me up
with another long neck
and put on "Everybody's
Working for the Weekend."
Shake your peach cobbler,
baby, good times!
He he!
[BUZZER]
- Oh hell, we got movie sign.
- Mike, you're such a Puritan.
[MIKE CRYING]
- That was pretty hot.
- We're not
going to a home down.
You want Leo to hire you
as a dancer or a dishwasher?
- You'd have to get
a gold hairnet, of course.
- This is from
the L.A. skank collection.
- You're about
the same size I am.
- Except you're misshapen
and horrible.
- Let's get you into these.
This is what you need to
show off what you got, baby.
- Let's see here,
oh, here we go.
Help wanted, burglar.
Cheap crabby idiot
needed immediately.
- Tell me
that's not seriously her.
Front page.
- Sure, the front page
of the L.A. Times,
"40 Dollar Robbery,
Nobody Hurt."
- Roda, are you home?
[CLEARS THROAT]
- The votive candles
seem out of place.
- Tada!
- Oh, she looks mildly
less frumpy.
- How do you like it?
- Beautiful.
- Now I can go to costume
parties dressed as margarine.
- One more time.
Here let me-- Terrific.
Let me help you.
- Let me help you with
your bowling balls here.
- Ah, Merry Christmas, I guess.
- Poke...
salad...
haha, whoo!
- Oh, that's good.
But we're casting
The Tempest here.
- Are they doing Feldenkrais?
- Man, it's been dark.
- Oh, no wonder.
- Well, okay, Buz,
you've had your fun.
Go on with the work.
- Sure thing, Leo.
- Mr. McCabe...
- Sure thing, Mrs. Miller--
Doh.
- This is how you frighten
a black bear in your camp.
Now let's try dancing.
- How do you not get hired
as a dancer here?
- Yeah.
I think she'll do.
Can you have her ready tonight?
- Well, there's license
and dealer prep, but yeah.
- She'll be ready, Leo.
- Good.
- Yeah!
Turn around, let me see.
- Hey--
Oh, bad cut!
- Well, my educated janitor.
Well, you look half human
with that beard gone.
- Don't let that fool you.
- How you doing?
- How would I know?
- Things going okay?
- Only one complaint.
- What's that?
- The water's too hard to make
a good bucket of suds.
- Aha, so this movie's
just a diatribe
for soft water pellets.
- Don't you remember
what I offered you?
Anytime you say, I could do
much better for you.
Much.
Well, a smart fella like you
shouldn't waste his time
mopping floors.
- I like this new
beardless vermin, Critter.
- Okay, so I plant my feet
and pretend to almost fall over.
- Hard water and stuff.
- Hey! It's me, honey.
Come on.
- And convulse!
And one and convulse.
[MOANING]
- Hey man, I've been going
around the block for 20 minutes.
- I don't even have
my earth shoes on.
- Twenty minutes
around a school yard?
The way you look,
they'll be busting you
for a deviant any second.
Come on, get out of here.
- Hey there, wait a minute,
I have a special order
for tomorrow morning.
- Blueberry waffles, man.
- I thought we were only
supposed to hit this spot
once a week, and that's all
we're going to hit it.
- Somebody better be here
tomorrow
or else you ain't
gonna be making
any more deliveries
in this neighborhood, baby.
- Eh, being Critter,
I better shred up some tissue
for my bedding tonight.
- Well, well.
- That's all
I have to say, bye.
- Aw, my faithful
traveling companion.
- See you been promoted
from yak boy to mop boy, huh?
- I have?
- How's your new job?
You get a chance
to murder anybody yet.
- Well, you know,
I've been trying,
but the-- hey!
- You stay away from Michele.
Look, you're not fooling anyone.
You still got your eye on her.
- It fell out on her,
I'm sorry.
- I admit,
I like Michele a lot.
Buz, do you honestly think
she'll ever be your girl?
- I'm warning you
because I won't leave
nothing but the pieces.
- I swear, I'll kill you.
Now hear
"Leaving on a Jet Plane."
- Buz?
- Need a backrub?
- You know, you're like
a blind rattlesnake.
You hear a noise
and you strike.
- Yeah, well,
you're like a deaf puff adder.
- You should try staying calm.
- Think of Perry Cuomo.
- Then you could think
and observe.
If you did that,
you'd know I'm no threat
to your love life.
- Get it? I'm G-A-Y.
- You're about as gutless
as this bike of yours.
- Why, if I weren't so tired,
I'd throw more
flowery language at you.
[BLUES MUSIC]
- Yeah.
- Many of these gals
went on to marry
some of the biggest scums
in L.A.
- These gals make me laugh
every time.
- Go, Mary Tyler Moore, go!
- Hey, Witchiepoo's
sitting there.
- Hey, get up there
and shake a tail feather.
- I hope she has some sort of
gel insert in her boots
so she doesn't get shin splints.
[TOM IMITATES SINGER]
- Hey, Geraldine.
CROW:
♪ Keep me in pot for the day ♪
- I really stink.
- Families love it.
- They're funnier
than the Rich Brothers.
- Little afternoon delight?
- Aaaaaaa.
Ah, forget it.
- Our Critter.
- We're celebrating
our anniversary.
- Marlo Thomas
and the Marlo-ettes.
- Brought to you
by the Gregory Method.
- It's not fun for me anymore.
That move really blew it.
- Man, I left the Jesuits
for this?
[CLAPPING AND CHEERING]
- Go team.
- Band thinks
everyone loves them.
- Mike, Mike, look,
underwear!
- I see it, I see it.
- I don't think I missed
a single step, did I?
- No, no babe, not a...
[indistinct]
- Great.
- Thank you for putting me
at the end of the line.
- That isn't your spot.
I just put you there
in case they noticed
you made a goof
or something.
But that spot belongs to
one of the other girls.
- Well, you just linger there.
- Starburst?
- Thank you.
You don't think it'll
make anyone mad, do you?
- So, let 'em find
another joint.
- Why do people
even go to movies
that don't feature underwear?
- I don't know.
- Here.
- Put on Bea Arthur's moo moo.
- ...put this on
and come out front with me.
- I want you to meet
some of the customers,
support the business.
- Looking into curtains.
- Goodbye underwear.
- That's for tomorrow night.
I want you to dance
in Joanie's place.
- Chachi won't let her dance
anymore.
- My intentions are honorable,
he he he.
- She needs a day off.
Besides, she's tired.
- Wait, I'm fine,
my suppos have refreshed me.
- Bah, my hair fell down.
- I'm almost out of pills
if I'm going to have a holiday.
It'd really be nicer, honey.
- I don't know.
Oh, by the way, I'm having
a little party later.
I'd like you there, okay?
- Sure.
- Later?
- I think the greasy pusher
likes me.
- Good luck with
your addiction, bye.
- Hey, now sit like
a proper junkie.
- Ah! Balloo!
- Man, if it gets
any wilder here,
a bridge game
is gonna break out.
- Why are they
in a different room?
- Ever seen a tick that big?
- It's actually a ham roll,
I didn't think you'd light it.
- Hey, suddenly I love
"The Almond Brothers."
- Come on, let's put on
"Sister Mary Elephants."
- Think this is
Dan Roan's life story.
- I'm gonna carve out
an apple and finish this.
- Well, I'm hungry
and paranoid, thanks.
- Where am I.
- Come to my dimension,
it's fun over here.
- You really look great
in that dress.
- Can I borrow it sometime?
- Thank you.
- Your glass is empty.
- Here, take mine,
I'm getting silly.
- Cheers.
- We better go home now, mom.
- So then the guy says,
"Dave's not here, man."
[LAUGHS]
- I bet you move pretty good.
- Can you help me
with my couch on Tuesday.
- Why don't you show me
what you really do.
Huh?
- Heh?
- Come on.
Groove, baby.
- Yeah.
- Groove.
- Aw, geez.
She sat in the clam dip.
- Hey, do you know...
[MAKES DRUM NOISES]
- Oh my goodness,
she's hepped up on the drugs.
- Dancin'
Bradley Stevenson there.
- Makes Elaine Benes
look like a good dancer.
- Thanks, that's most exciting.
- I'm over here.
- Whatever, white people.
- When sexy becomes annoying.
- Heh heh heh.
- Yeah, yeah sure.
It's fun
'til someone loses an eye.
- Next Kitty Carlisle
will read Howl.
- Yeah yeah yeah, right
right right, uh-huh,
yeah yeah yeah...
[BLUES MUSIC]
- Ooo yeah!
- Hey, that's her
Gore-Tex winter bra.
[TOM SINGS WITH MUSIC]
- Oh yeah,
you're worth some steam, baby.
- I should wear a bikini.
- My mom's card parties
used to end up like this.
- ♪ ...keep your gold boots
Moving... ♪
- ♪ Or your silver ones ♪
♪ We don't mean
To discriminate ♪
♪ Against the other
Color boots ♪
- Whoo!
- Do the wounded turkey.
[TURKEY GOBBLE]
- Boy, I'm glad Oliver Platt
didn't get this role.
- Yeah.
- Now it's kind of like
vaguely sexual wallpaper.
[CHEERING]
- I couldn't possibly go farther
in show business.
- Thank you, I hope
that in my small way,
I've kept my gold boots moving,
thank you.
Thank you.
- Well, well.
Glad to see
somebody made it.
You know, I hate doing business
with leery people like Marty,
you know what I mean?
That's how people get...
popped.
- Arafat in the 60s.
- Where's the junk.
- Relax, live a little bit.
I mean, what's the use of
passing all of this bread
if we can't have fun,
right, baby?
- Ew.
- Ha-ha-ha, we're icky.
- You know, for a new guy,
you're sure learning fast.
- He-he, pushing's fun.
- The money first, huh?
- What's the matter?
Don't you trust me, Buzzy?
- [indistinct].
- I wouldn't trust you
with a care package.
[CHUCKLES]
- Well, it's sweaty and
it's got a crew x on it, but...
- Hey, Joey.
Why don't you look
at the tire, huh?
- Sure, I enjoy a good radial
as much as the next guy.
- Man, this thing is coated
with squirrel guts.
- Hey, see you next Friday,
Buzzy.
Second and Main, huh?
Don't forget, two P.M.
- Okay, baby.
- See you later, Buzzy.
- Oh, I hope he comes to
the pusher's Christmas party.
- I take pride in knowing
I provide the kids
quality drugs
at reasonable prices.
- Excuse me, young fellow,
can I get a fix?
- Really, I'm very strung out
and in need of some Mary Jane
or some reefer.
- Slipping on filth is fun.
- Thought you could
break up with me, huh?
- Please, don't explain my...
[indistinct] to me, please.
- It's Tab Hunters.
- Did you guys ever notice
those girls in front of us
when we play?
What's that about?
- Hey man, hold it.
- Hey, someone's taking Schmidt
guitar lessons back there.
- Who's that?
- I don't know,
but I like it.
- Look at these hippies,
get a haircut!
- I keep missing the strings.
- Hi.
Hello.
I was just listening in,
what's the name of that tune.
- I call it lousy.
- Doesn't really
have a name yet.
I been thinking
about calling it,
"Do You Want To Laugh Or Cry?"
- That's one of yours?
I liked it.
Has a good sound.
Oh, I'm Chris Howard.
- Who cares?
- Critter Jones.
- You have this thing
written down?
- Just the words.
Never dreamed anyone else
would want to play it.
- Well, why don't you
come on up front.
Let's give it to the guys.
I'd like to see what
they could do with it, okay?
- Sure.
- I really enjoyed
that one bar.
- You have any more of those?
- Yeah, I've got a bunch
lying around.
- Great, 'cause we may
want to burn them
or crap on them
or something.
[♪♪♪]
- Hey, My Three Sons grew up
and started a band.
Then hired two other guys,
I guess.
- Kevin Spacey and
William Holden enjoy the show.
- One-he and a two-he
and a-- oh damn.
[MIKE IMITATES GUITAR]
- No, no.
It's not working.
Maybe what I heard
this morning
was the furnace
kicking in or something.
- ♪ Do you want to laugh
Or cry ♪
MIKE:
♪ Or look like John Tesh ♪
- If you gentlemen
will excuse me.
- Oh, you don't
have to go yet, baby.
- Yes, I have to get changed
for my next show.
- Don't be too long.
[♪♪♪]
- Man, who wrote that turd
of a song out there?
Pee-yoo.
- Now I won't have to say
goodbye to you in a note.
- I'm gonna say it
in semaphore flags.
- Are you really leaving
this time, Critter?
- Yes.
- Soon as I finish my sculpture
of Devil's Tower.
- If you take a good look
around you,
you would too.
Close the door.
- Be on the other side of it.
- Sit down.
- You've probably
never got up before,
so let me show you how.
- Leo deals in narcotics.
LSD and you name it.
And Buz is up to here
in it with him.
- So?
- Well, I think they should
expand into Angel Dust.
- I sold a couple of songs today
for a hundred bucks.
And you can have half.
- Some guy paid me
to destroy them.
- Fifty dollars?
More than anyone else
has offered me.
You don't even want me.
- Hey, I'm not trying
to be funny.
- Man, I wish that were true
of Jim Carey.
- I was afraid you weren't.
- So, can I add
to your autograph?
- Look Michele, you can't afford
to get mixed up with this bunch.
- Who says I have to get
mixed up with anyone?
- I was just lap dancing
for some old guys, that's all.
- Listen to me, Michele.
The pigs of this world
won't let you
sit on this fence
above the mud
and watch the action
for very long.
- They want corn husks.
- You either run
when they spot you,
or they'll pull you down.
Then you have no choice.
Now I say they have us spotted
and it's time we find
a new fence
to straddle for a while.
- Not a chain link though,
that would hurt.
- Just ask me to go away
with you and I will.
- What in the devil do you think
I've been doing?
- I mean, ask me
because you want me.
Because you need me.
- Doesn't matter
what I want or need.
- Critter.
- Where? Oh-oh.
- ...please tell me
that you love me.
Then I'll go away with you.
We can get out of
here together.
- Tell you a thing like that?
And then have you hate my guts
when you find out about me?
- Huh?
- Not on your life, baby.
- Find out about what?
- Alright.
You asked for it.
- I don't like potatoes.
- You think I'm just
a college dropout
in the Peace Corps.
Well, I'm much bigger
than that.
- I'm Adolf Hitler.
- Next week I'll be on
the wanted list of the FBI.
Finley Jones,
alias Critter Jones.
- Alias Smith and Jones.
- Wanted for refusal
to serve his country
in time of
a national emergency.
- Are you supposed to be
in the army?
- Next week I'm supposed to be,
only I won't.
- A draft dodger, you?
- I don't know.
All I know is that I've gotta
find a hole to crawl into
so they can't find me.
- Talk to Courtney Love.
- That's the kind of man I am.
One that's got to find
a hole to crawl into.
- Alright, you find your hole.
Me? I'm staying here.
Why should I leave?
Leo says I'm really
going places.
Just because he deals in dope,
that doesn't tarnish me.
- Oh that's what you think,
baby.
Tarnish isn't
a strong enough word
for what he'll do to you.
Try corrode for size.
- Yeah, corrode, great.
- Why don't you take
a good look at Joanie.
She's been places with Leo.
And there's a trashy book
written on every line
on her face.
- Aren't you the great one.
- Gretzky?
- Solving other people's
problems.
- Hey, I polished
my shirt for you.
- Bad Traveler, bad boy.
- So he became a buster
in the London tubes.
- ♪ I love her lips
The touch of her hand ♪
♪ I love her eyes
The way they shine ♪
MIKE:
♪ If I could save
Time in bottle... ♪
- ♪ ...I need makes my heart ♪
- One of Morrissey's
more upbeat songs.
- I guess he's got a microphone
implanted in his throat.
- I can't go out with you
because I'm considerably
bigger than you.
- What's that over there?
[HUMMING]
- I'm gonna take off,
I'm meeting someone for lunch.
- You gonna tune
that D-string there?
[IMITATES GUITAR TUNING]
- He gets a nice harmonica sound
out of that guitar there.
TOM:
♪ Morgan David and... ♪
♪ [indistinct]
...Manischewitz ♪
- Say, I just remembered,
could you return
that one book I lent you?
- Okay then, I'm not
coming back this time.
- Draft board just called
and told him, never mind.
- Don't ask, don't sing.
- Look, I'm getting
a little annoyed with you
summoning me back here
every five seconds.
- Could you at least get
your guitar neck out of my ear?
- Oh, I see, Critter.
You're giving them
your version.
TOM:
♪ Oh oh bitter dregs ♪
CROW:
♪ Oh fur lined bras ♪
- Yeah.
- Underwear, underwear.
- Whoo.
- ♪ You lips are slender
Your eyes are blue ♪
♪ Your hair is blonde
Your lips the way they're red ♪
♪ Your skin your fingers
Your ears your nose ♪
♪ Your touch your feet
I am sad Oh ♪
- Uh, Mike?
The water there,
it got into a few spots.
There's a small fire.
Well, that's okay.
We'll get it.
- ♪ Oh ♪
♪ I need you so much
I fall down and cry... ♪
- Mike, look.
Uh, I'll wait.
♪ ...you're like wine ♪
- Uh, Mike?
The fire's a little worse
that we thought.
It must've gotten into
some insulation or something.
Ooo boy.
- ♪ Oh ♪
♪ I woo many ladies
They are fair ladies all... ♪
- Look Mike,
what we need you to do
is to move out
of that part of the ship.
- ♪ Raindrops and snowflakes
And poppies ♪
- Mike! Would you forget
about the raindrops
and the poppies
and get out!
Life support is failing,
decks three through seven
are gone.
Oh my God,
Servo, look out!
[SCREAMING]
- ♪ ...eyes they're like wine ♪
- Uh, yeah, Mike.
We got it.
[COUGHING]
There's still a lot of smoke
and water down here,
but as far as we know,
it's out.
Look, we're gonna go
make some nachos, okay?
- Nachos?
Whoa, be right there.
- ♪ Oh ♪
- Well, eh?
- Yeah.
This is the new dancer,
just wanted to get 'em
a locker and a gold bikini.
- Well mister, if you're a cop,
I want you to know
I'm not responsible
for this in any way...
[indistinct]
...it just so happens
he's the brother
of one of my dancers.
He blew in last night
from back east.
- A cop? Heaven forbid.
No, I'm no cop.
However I am associated
with the police,
rather closely associated.
- He... [indistinct]
...but he's got
one beautiful scam now.
You better listen
what he has to say, huh?
- Uh, boss, you gonna
take your shot?
- Since when did you start
telling me what I should hear?
- At the company retreat,
you said you'd be
more open to ideas.
- What do you want?
- Well, you see, one of
my best friends is a hophead.
- You have my sympathies.
- There's no need
for concern...
- Mary Tyrone?
- ...he's well fed by a sort of
a foster mother named Joey.
- Never heard of him.
- It's just as well.
I'm sure that you prefer
a higher degree of intelligence
in your employees.
Joey isn't very bright.
He proved that
by not listening to my story.
- Boy, he sounds
pretty smart to me.
- Poor Joey is also
not very careful.
When he refused to listen,
it became necessary for me
to follow him and speak
to his connections.
Young man with
far more on the ball.
You might find it expedient
to promote him.
- Really?
- Yeah, Dad, I've really
learned a lot about drugs.
- Of course,
this is no surprise to me.
Connections should always
be smarter than the pusher.
If he weren't,
then he would be the pusher
and the pusher would be he.
- Leo, Leo, Leo, look.
He told me he's a trustee
at the Eastwood County Jail
about 40 miles from here.
- And I've been a guest there
on other occasions.
- Yeah, yeah.
And he says
the narcotics squad out there
made a big hit last weekend.
Leo, they picked up over
100,000 dollars worth of stuff.
- They keep it
in an empty cell at the jail,
locked of course.
Now that's where
I enter the picture once more.
- I suppose you got the keys?
- Fella, I'd never steal
anything as worthless as a key.
Your desk locked?
- I need a paperclip
to clean my ears.
- Yeah, why?
- Excuse me.
- I'm gonna go over here
and fart.
- So, gonna get in a caper
with Grover Cleveland.
- What are you doing?
- Sir, I'm going to give you
100,000 dollar demonstration
in 10 seconds.
- Man, that's disgusting.
- Broke the key of
in the lock.
- Now that cell door
is much easier.
- Oh, got me a fresh sack
of Critter pellets.
- ...and you only want a third.
- Well, I've been
thinking of retiring
and my wants are quite simple,
really.
- Easy Cheese and Cannon reruns.
- Tonight, I shall get
good and drunk.
- It's good to have dreams,
I guess.
- Tomorrow, I'll be at
Eastwood County Jail
with their number one trustee.
- The head of Otis?
- I need only one brave man.
- I think I know you,
what's your name?
- Uh, the boy'll do.
- Boy?
- Even if he does think
I'm nutty.
- What's your name?
- Bob Ovalhead.
- Blatz.
Harry Blatz.
- I brewed a pretty crumby beer,
I admit it.
- Well, I have a private meeting
in my oil tank.
- Excuse me, Mr. Blatz,
while I have a talk
with this bright young man.
- I don't think he's so young,
the guy's in his 40s.
- I don't know...
- This guy's no Joseph Coors.
- You tell me.
Can you get it?
- What, The Knack?
- You mean,
I can go with Harry?
- If you can get back here
with the stuff
without the cops, yeah.
But if you bungle it...
- No Circus Pizza later.
- Remember...
I don't know you.
Now where's my money?
- I spent it all
on these magic beans!
- Wow, a young kid like me,
breaking into crime.
- Hear that, Traveler?
- Yeah, the boys
tried to take him on
but he grabbed
one of their flashlights
and threw it through
the plate glass window.
- Me? Oh, I'm still ugly.
- Well hell, if he wants to
live off the county,
he can go to
the welfare department.
Judge'll probably give him
10 days this time.
I'm going to work his tail off
all the time.
- So, you called 911.
What's up?
- Okay, bye.
- Boy, the murders
are stacking up.
- Man, you know if you're
the town drunk of L.A.,
you've got a problem.
- Alright Harry,
let's get some work down.
- He uses his one call
to have liquor delivered.
- Now my widow's peak
snaps into action.
- Oh, we had another
bloody Christmas episode
in the holding cell.
Clean it up, would you?
- I think prison garbage
would be damper than that, Mike.
[BUZZER]
- The true story of the great
Mendocino County garbage heist.
- Good thing
he's so young and agile.
- He's just a kid,
be careful up there.
- Whoa, big neck cramp.
- So young.
Very young.
- Can't keep all this
luscious refuse to myself.
- Here, this'll give you
something to do
with those busy hands.
- What is he implying?
- Okay, whatta we do now?
- Just follow me
and act as if you live here.
- Ah, remember
when the movie was just
hot girls dancing around?
- Oh yeah.
- Just about time
for my Jerry Orbach lesson.
[BUZZER]
- I reproduced asexually
while I was out, sir.
- Tonight, on Oz.
- Morning, Otis.
- Harry, I thought
you had got out.
- Well, I have returned.
- You oughta lay
off that stuff.
Man, when I get out of here,
I don't want to ever see
the inside of this place again.
[LAUGHS]
- Uh, Otis?
Say hello to Buz.
- Buz, whatcha in for?
- His wife claims
that he beat her up.
- You know how broads are.
- No, tell me.
I've been in here 18 months.
- Well, enough of
the chit chat, boys.
We best get on
with our duties.
I don't want to be responsible
for you going on bread and water
on your very first day.
- Although, they do make a great
rosemary and onion focaccia.
- What are you trying to do?
- Merely establish a witness
in case I should ever
find a need of one.
- Well I don't like it.
- There's nothing to be
concerned about.
He has no way to finger you
without my help.
- Well, since you're wearing
a jumpsuit...
- You see, I've been planning
my retirement for some time.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Let's go.
- There's some garbage
in the men's room
I'm just itching
to get my hands on.
- This place could use a plant
or a kitten poster or something.
- At least one of those
motivational posters.
- Yeah, you know like,
"You can get out jail,
you can escape."
- Well, thanks for
getting me in here.
I'll see you in the soup line
tomorrow.
- Well, open it up.
- No, I mean your jumpsuit.
- Come on.
- See now, he's breaking
further into jail.
That doesn't seem very wise.
- You go.
- Don't worry.
All my little precautions
have now been taken.
From here on,
it's as easy as
hauling off
the proverbial dollar.
- No, don't, you idiot!
What are you...
- Take the satchels,
put them into the waste basket,
you carry them to your car
and drive away.
And I won't mind
seeing you go.
Of course, I know
that there is now only one way
you can keep
from paying me my share.
- Yup, that's the way.
You figured out how to do it.
Beating in my skull
with a tire iron.
Oh, there's my brains
on the floor.
- Harry Blatz is dead.
Falling water signs
have stopped for the day.
- Yes, my plan is perfect.
I've been spotted
by several people
and I killed a guy.
Heh heh.
- Well, what can you expect,
he's just a child.
[♪♪♪]
- You may think
the success with Leo
and all the cooks
in this joint
mean you got the
world by the tail.
But that ain't the case, baby.
It's got you by the tail.
- Man, she put on seven pairs
of false eyelashes
and didn't notice.
- So, you going
to the company picnic?
- Crack, now in easy
to take crack caplets.
- You,
you wouldn't believe it
but I came to this town
four years ago.
And I was just as young
and as fresh...
- As Marianne Faithful.
- ...as you are right now.
And see this hand?
It was steady as a rock.
- Then I saved Private Ryan.
- And I had a pretty mind.
- I used to dress it up
in nice clothes.
- I had a pretty mind!
- Then my mind had babies
and got stretch marks.
- Oh.
Oh. I had,
I had a pretty mind.
- Yeah, well, so can I borrow
your lipstick or not?
- Don't! Don't!
- The Laurel and Hardy
of strippers.
- Don't!
Help!
Help me please!
- Her false eyelashes
are smothering her!
- Help!
- Dr. Critter.
- Michele, get that junk off...
- Scrape it off,
steam it off--
Eh, you better
just boil the couch.
- What happened?
- I don't know.
She just fainted.
- She took three pounds
of heroin and just fainted.
I don't know what happened.
- Great, now I gotta
drag her out on stage
and take her clothes off
manually.
- I'm sure you know
what's wrong with her, Leo.
- You used to be on staff
at the Mayo Clinic.
- Well, knowing Joanie,
I can imagine, Critter.
She's probably on a bad trip
from those pills she takes.
- She did take one
not long before she fainted.
- One?
It's not the first time
this has happened.
It's become a habit with her.
- Somebody'd better
call a doctor.
- Nobody's calling a doctor.
- I'm a Christian Scientist.
- She'll survive
the way she always does.
- Wow, his head must've
brushed against the ceiling.
- You know, maybe it's too bad
she will survive.
- She has to save my back
tonight.
- She used to be
a good dancer.
She still is,
but she's losing her spark.
Besides, he's old hat
with the customers.
- She's a straw boater?
- Michele?
You may be the luckiest girl
in Hollywood.
- No, that would be
Lea Thompson.
- You've got what it takes
to really blow their minds
and a little more to boot.
- Yeah, really blow their minds.
- So, starting tonight, you'll
replace Joanie permanently.
And you'll be the number one
attraction here.
- I couldn't do that to Joan.
- [LAUGHS]
I bet you can.
- He's a tower of oil.
- And if it'll ease
your conscience,
then let me tell you,
she wouldn't bat an eye
stomping on you.
And if you don't take her place,
somebody else will.
- Like Charles Durning.
- All this means an apartment
like Joan's, a car...
- Plymouth Sundance.
- ...a wardrobe,
a name up in lights.
Believe me, baby,
there ain't nothing
like the sound of people
clapping for you
night after night.
- Getting the clap
night after night
is a different thing,
of course.
[GROANING]
- Oh, I'm a lectern
at church today, am I late?
- Look what,
look what it's done for me.
- Now this is a nice scene.
- Yeah, it's sweet.
- Get out of here.
Get out of here!
Get out. Get out.
- Who do you think
you're talking to?
- I'm talking to you!
- Pleasant.
- I've already left here!
- You shut up!
You shut up, you trashy bitch!
- Hey!
- Oh.
- I'm running to Staples,
you need anything?
- You're not big.
- Wow, I'll check
the employee handbook,
but I think
that's out of line.
- Get out.
[SCREAMS]
[ALL COMMENTATORS LAUGHING]
- Okay.
Man, even the sex and drug
industry has a seedier side.
- Leo?
Got the good stuff right here.
Everything went off great.
Just great.
- Killed a guy though.
- And old Harry Blatz retired
earlier than he planned to.
- Shut up.
Old Harry...
just who is this Harry Blatz?
How do you know the name
Harry Blatz, Critter?
- Look what I found under here,
I'm just gonna...
- Look, what you guys do
is no business of mine.
You're playing a game
I don't know,
and one I don't want to know.
So, if you don't mind,
I'll just take my leave.
Come on, Michele,
you're going with me.
- It's a little late
for that decision, friend.
You are involved.
You're not going any place.
Get in here.
- Uh, how long you been saving
that sight gag, Mike?
- Oh, not long, you know,
I don't know.
Eight years.
- ...pigs have finally
pulled us down.
- Sit down.
- Oh, that hurts!
- Splash.
Splash!
- This scene, sponsored
by Paneling World.
Paneling World,
for all your paneling needs.
- No!
- Don't get hair grease
on the pool table.
- Yeah, don't.
- My complexion.
- When nominal group process
gets out of control.
- Yah, see?
- You're killing him!
- Oh please,
I'm susceptible, see?
Stop it, my sister.
- Well there goes his
conscientious objector status.
- Wow.
- Losing oil.
- Gulp.
- Okay.
Okay.
You've made your point.
- We'll get the damn
water softener.
Take your girl
and get out of here.
- Uh-uh.
The muck's too deep in here.
- Well, it's your fault,
you're the janitor.
- Look, just take a stripper
out of petty cash
and leave, huh?
- Um, you have to dial nine.
- Operator?
Get me the police department.
- Hello? Ocean?
No, this isn't the police,
Mr. Critter.
No, don't worry,
we're one number off.
We get those calls a lot.
That's okay.
Oh boy, now.
- Man, those signs
are close together
if you're going 65.
- Oh! So, we learned
he enjoys violence
and he's ready to kill
like a man oughta.
- Ah, so she stopped dancing,
and she's in a barber shop
quartet now I guess.
- Oh boy,
how'd I get into this.
She's dumb as a brick.
Hi, honey.
- No, no.
Honey, you promised me
you'd throw your guitar
in the ocean!
- ♪ You can dance
On the rim of a rainbow ♪
♪ Walking tight rope
Across the sky ♪
♪ But you must come down ♪
♪ Put your feet on the ground
By and by ♪
- Do the giant toddler dance.
- ♪ You can shoot the curl
Free and easy ♪
- Honey, way to play
the harmonica with your ass!
- ♪ But you must come down ♪
♪ Put your feet
In the sand once more ♪
- So here's a puzzler,
who of these two
is worse at their art form?
- Wow.
That's deep, man.
- ♪ ...a love with no end ♪
- She's dancing the special
to TGI Friday's.
- Well, I hope she tells us
in dance
about the Jack Daniels grill.
- ♪ But you must come down ♪
♪ Put your feet on the ground
By and by ♪
TOM:
♪ You're living a lie ♪
- ♪ You gotta come down ♪
TOM:
♪ You dance like a clown ♪
- ♪ By and by ♪
TOM:
♪ I hope that you die ♪
- Alright.
I wonder if her dad'll
give her away at the wedding.
- Yeah, he'll probably
try to sell her, actually.
- No, I bet Dad's cleaned up
since we saw him
and now he owns
a chain of "Eats."
[BLUES MUSIC]
MIKE:
♪ Remember the beginning ♪
♪ This is just
Like the beginning ♪
♪ It's just like the beginning
Yeah girls ♪
- Filmed on location at "Eat."
- And special thank to "Eat."
CROW:
♪ And I just can't get
Of this one note ♪
♪ Keep your silver bra
Filled with breast ♪
- Heh heh heh.
Heh heh heh.
- Heh heh heh...
Hey.
We're all dressed like
that ugly thug in the movie.
- Yeah. Heh heh heh...
ALL:
Heh heh heh...
- Ah, hmm.
- So, your experiment
calls them to dress
as Armenian mobsters
and giggle?
- Look at those poor dopes
writhing in pain.
Whatta ya think, huh?
Pretty highfalutin mad science.
Ha-ha!
- Right, not even fit for
a guest spot on Beakman's World.
- What? No, I am evil.
I even went and took
and killed my monkey for you.
- What?
- Oh, shut up and die, fathead.
- I'm off!
- No, sir, come on.
You can't leave.
I have to take over the world.
- There's absolutely nothing
truly evil going on.
Yeah?
Wait a minute.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes.
Forester, this is mad.
Well, decidedly mad.
You showed us something
quite new.
- It is new, isn't it?
- It's absolutely horrifying.
Alright, Forester.
You're in, conditionally.
Can he... pony?
- Can I pony?
- If we can harness
this level of terror,
we could rule the world!
[LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
- Oh God.
I had such a pretty mind.
ANNOUNCER:
Produced in association
with the Sci-Fi Channel.